<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Products &amp; Services on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/</link><description>Recent content in Products &amp; Services on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access Control</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/access-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/access-control/</guid><description>Next Gen Firewall A next-generation firewall (NGFW) is a hardware- or software-based network security system that is able to detect and block sophisticated attacks by enforcing security policies at the application level, as well as at the port and protocol level. Internal Firewall This is a device similar to a next generation firewall but deployed to monitor internal traffic in an organization Unified Threat Management UTM is the evolution of the traditional firewall into an all-inclusive security product able to perform multiple security functions within one single system: network firewalling, network intrusion detection/prevention (IDS/IPS), gateway antivirus (AV), gateway anti-spam, VPN, content filtering, load balancing, data loss prevention, and on-appliance reporting.</description></item><item><title>Accessories</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/accessories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/accessories/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Active Networks</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/active-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/active-networks/</guid><description>About Active Networks Active networks refer to the live part of the network, including the operations policies and management procedures.
Businesses today are in the midst of massive transformation in which the world has become the new workplace. To be part of this quickly evolving business landscape, you need to concentrate on becoming more agile, more efficient, and more competitive in the market place.
For any business, active networks today are required in order to be secure, reliable, and connectable seamlessly anywhere, anytime, for any user, and on any device.</description></item><item><title>Anti Virus</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/anti-virus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/anti-virus/</guid><description>Computech offers multi-vendor options based on your custom requirements for anti-virus and internet security software.</description></item><item><title>Asset Protection</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/asset-protection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/asset-protection/</guid><description>Advanced Threat Protection An advanced persistent threat (APT) is a network attack in which an unauthorized person gains access to a network and stays there undetected for a long period of time. The intention of an APT attack is to steal data rather than to cause damage to the network or organization. Sandboxing a sandbox is a security mechanism for separating running programs. It is often used to execute untested or untrusted programs or code, possibly from unverified or untrusted third parties, suppliers, users or websites, without risking harm to the host machine or operating system.</description></item><item><title>ATMS &amp; Banking</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/atms-banking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/atms-banking/</guid><description>Computech Partners with the best in the industry, Diebold Nixdorf Computech Limited’s partnership with Diebold Nixdorf began in 2013, when Computech was appointed as an agent in Zambia. Since then, the partnership has flourished with Computech’s focus on customer service aligning with Diebold Nixdorf’s and Computech ability to implement and advise on Diebold Nixdorf’s extensive range of solutions to meet customer needs.
Diebold Nixdorf is a world leader in driving connected commerce, bridging the gap between the physical and digital worlds of cash.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Replication</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/backup-replication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/backup-replication/</guid><description>Back up Backup refers to the process of copying and archiving of computer data so it may be used to restore the original after a data loss event
Replication Replication is the frequent electronic copying of data from a database in one computer or server to a database in another so that all users share the same level of information.
Computech Limited offers data Backup and Replication services, based on your needs and requirements.</description></item><item><title>cisco</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cisco/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cisco/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Compute</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/compute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/compute/</guid><description>About Compute solutions Computing infrastructure is behind many company applications and data in the form of delivering accessibility, availability, security and ensuring the integrity of critical information assets.
With the advances in technology real-time analytics, server and application virtualization, high performance computing (HPC) are within the reach of the average business but not all CPUs and server architectures are created the same. Different workloads and applications have different performance characteristics and therefore may demand different computing resources.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Security</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/cyber-security/</guid><description>Access Control Asset Protection Reaction &amp;amp; recovery Visibility Need Assistance? Feel free to talk to us ! Full Name Email Phone Organization / Company Country Message SEND</description></item><item><title>Data Centre</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/data-centres/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/data-centres/</guid><description>About Data Centres Known as the server farm or the computer room, the data center is where the majority of an enterprise servers and storage are located, operated and managed.
White space: This typically refers to the usable raised floor environment measured in square feet (anywhere from a few hundred to a hundred thousand square feet). For data centers that don’t use a raised floor environment, the term &amp;lsquo;white space&amp;rsquo; may still be used to show usable square footage.</description></item><item><title>Desktops</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/desktops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/desktops/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Diagnostic Imaging</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/diagnostic-imaging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/diagnostic-imaging/</guid><description>DGS Radiography GE’s fixed radiology systems are available in both the Digital and Analogue version, depending on your needs. The Digital systems are more technically advanced and so able to do more. The analogue systems can be easily upgraded to Digital and are known for their simplicity, reliability and crisp images
Mobile radiography systems provide the same reliability, sharp image output and simplicity of use but with the ability to move wherever needed</description></item><item><title>Endpoint Devices</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/</guid><description>Accessories desktops Laptops printers Projectors &amp;amp; Screens Tablets Need Assistance? Feel free to talk to us ! Full Name Email Phone Organization / Company Country Message SEND</description></item><item><title>Healthcare</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/</guid><description>Diagnostic Imaging Ultrasound In 2015, Computech Limited was appointed Independent Channel Partner (ICP) for General Electric Healthcare. Computech’s portfolio covers Digital Imaging including MRI, CT scanners, and X-Ray machines, and Ultrasound for both Tanzania and Uganda.
GE Healthcare provides transformational medical technologies and services that are shaping a new age of patient care.
GE Healthcare, a unit of General Electric Company, is one of the world’s leading organisations dedicated to health.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/</guid><description>BACKUP &amp;amp; REPLICATION COMPUTE DATA CENTRES PHYSICAL SECURITY SOLUTIONS STORAGE</description></item><item><title>Laptops</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/laptops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/laptops/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Leasing</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/leasing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/leasing/</guid><description>Partners What is Leasing? A lease is an extended rental agreement under which the owner of the equipment allows the user to operate or make use of the equipment for a set fee.
Computech provides leasing options for servers and PCs, providing the best service and maintenance to ensure optimal equipment performance. Leasing allows our customers to take advantage of equipment upgrades and minimize downtime.
What are the advantages of Leasing?</description></item><item><title>Maintenance</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/maintenance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/maintenance/</guid><description>Clients What is Maintenance? Maintenance involves regular check-ups of machines and equipment, including physical cleaning and diagnostics. The Computech team regularly conducts preventative maintenance exercise on a bi-annual or quarterly basis for customers, ensuring optimum performance of machines.
What are the benefits of Maintenance by Computech? Optimum performance of machines Proactive checks on hardware to prevent potential issues Availability of highly skilled professional team able to guarantee quality and performance of equipment Access to discounts on original manufacture spare parts</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Solutions</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/microsoft-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/microsoft-solutions/</guid><description>Computech Limited is a Microsoft Preferred Partner and Kenya’s top Enterprise Licensing Advisory. We are Gold in Cloud Productivity and have one of the most locally certified teams, with one of the largest outsourced Level 1 &amp;amp; 2 support teams in Eastern Africa.
Microsoft Cloud Microsoft Managed Services Microsoft Licensing Computech Webstore</description></item><item><title>Outsourcing</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/outsourcing/</guid><description>Partners What is Outsourcing? IT Outsourcing involves Computech performing IT related tasks and services for our clients, including Level 1 and Level 2 support. We have significant experience with data centre management, service desk and workplace management, and end to end support on networking practice.
What are the advantages of Outsourcing? Reduces IT costs and expenditure Increases efficiency Allows client to focus on Core Business Areas Provides access to expertise and skilled resources Saves on infrastructure and technology Optimizes resource utilization and enhance organizational adaptability</description></item><item><title>Passive Networks</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/passive-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/passive-networks/</guid><description>About Passive Networks Computech provides cabling and network solutions, including installation of horizontal cabling for all offices, vertical backbone cabling in buildings, smart building solutions to increase building value and rental yields, as well as integrated network solutions.
We are able to provide a managed service level agreement for all our customers, covering horizontal and vertical cabling, and offer specific industry based solutions. Our work developing network plans includes switches and wifi solutions and our integrated network solutions include providing virtual private networks (VPNs) for connectivity to a closed group of users and subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Physical Security Solutions</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/physical-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/physical-security-solutions/</guid><description>CCTV image Fire alarm system image Speaker system image (public address) About Physical Security Solutions Physical security involves ensuring the safety of your building, whether an office, hotel, or apartment building. All businesses, whether small, medium or large, have assets that need to be protected from theft, as well as protecting staff and their property. Issues addressed by these solutions include managing access, monitoring activity, fire alarm and suppression systems, protection from intruders and speaker systems for announcements.</description></item><item><title>Printers</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/printers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/printers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projectors &amp; Screens</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/projectors-screens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/projectors-screens/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/services/</guid><description>Leasing Maintenance Outsourcing</description></item><item><title>Software Solutions</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/</guid><description>anti-virus custom software solutions Microsoft Solutions</description></item><item><title>Software Solutions</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/custom-software-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/software-solutions/custom-software-solutions/</guid><description>Enterprise Loyalty Dynamic pricing Business process management Proof of delivery A Zafin Labs solution that provides the ability to Create Loyalty across the entire banking portfolio as opposed to conventional credit cards. The solution promotes cross selling, reduces customer attrition, and increases loyalty toward the brand instead of generating loyalty for a particular benefit. A high value solution promoting revenue growth and customer centricity which is currently used by 30 banks globally.</description></item><item><title>Storage</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/infrastructure/storage/</guid><description>About Storage solutions In today’s world, data must be available 24x7. If a customer’s IT infrastructure is disrupted, it can mean much more than a temporary loss of computing power. Work delays, data degradation, and data loss can quickly translate into lost revenue, lost profits, and lost customers. As more and more applications are deemed “mission critical”, customers are challenged to maintain appropriate levels of access, availability, and security.</description></item><item><title>Tablets</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/tablets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/endpoint-devices/tablets/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ultrasound</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/ultrasound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/products-services/healthcare/ultrasound/</guid><description>Ultrasound uses sound waves to develop images of the body’s internal functions which are relayed in real time to monitors to help doctors make decisions about the care to give their patients
There are various uses for Ultrasound: Pregnancy confirmation and check-ups Diagnosis of organs (e.g. liver, gall bladder, heart) Medical procedures such as taking biopsies GE Ultrasound machines are created with each individual use in mind. All machines are robust, easy to use and many allow the clinician to create preferences to suit their particular requirement</description></item></channel></rss>