<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>event on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/event/</link><description>Recent content in event on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dell CIO Breakfast</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-cio-event/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-cio-event/</guid><description>Dell technologies and Computech hosted a CIO breakfast targeting companies in the Financial sector at Movenpick Hotel on the 17th of July 2019. The event was graced by the Vice President Emerging Africa at Dell Technologies Habib Mahakian and Founder and CEO of Computech Limited Hassan Popat with the joint message that together they are here to support and cater to IT needs across East Africa. “We are excited about the partnership with Computech and what we want to do across Africa.</description></item><item><title>World Youth Skills Day</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/world-youth-skills-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/world-youth-skills-day/</guid><description>According to the @UN there are 1.2 billion young people aged 15 to 24 years, accounting for 16 per cent of the global population. The active engagement of youth in sustainable development efforts is central to achieving sustainable, inclusive and stable societies. Let&amp;rsquo;s celebrate World Youth Skills Day. Computech is always looking for ways to tap the potential that the youth exude. Meet Grace Wamuti #WYSD2019 #WeareComputech #WomeninIT #YouthSkillsDay #youthempowerment</description></item><item><title>Palo Alto Breakfast Workshop</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/palo-alto-workshop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/palo-alto-workshop/</guid><description>Westcon-Comstor held a breakfast workshop session on Palo Alto Networks focusing on the Next generation Firewall. Let us know if you want to test drive it. &amp;ldquo;Getting customers to have PROACTIVE PROTECTION is most important. Palo Alto Networks is focused on making the world safer everyday&amp;rdquo; ~ Said Rechchard, Africa Regional Sales Director at Palo Alto Networks
#WeAreComputech #FirewallZeroHour #PaloAlto www.computechlimited.com</description></item><item><title>HP Awards 2019</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-awards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-awards/</guid><description>Computech Limited is the HP corporate and enterprise partner of the year 2018 in East Africa. We were awarded during the HP channels Awards 2019 at Kempinski hotel on 25th June 2019. We are excited about this partnership as we continue to strive to meet our customers’ needs. #wearecomputech</description></item><item><title>Hpe Selectium Koroga</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hpe-koroga/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hpe-koroga/</guid><description>Nothing beats the enjoyment of cooking dinner at your work place and watching your bosses do all the cooking. Selectium and Computech got the chance to have a Koroga and get to know each other and strengthen its partnership. As Computech we are always looking at ways to improve our partnerships and offer you our customers the best Solutions #Wearecomputech #HPESelectium #Koroga</description></item><item><title>Cisco Connect</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/cisco-connect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/cisco-connect/</guid><description>The Cisco Connect SSA was held at Sun City, South Africa from 19th-21st May 2019. Computech was a proud sponsor for this event and we appreciate all the partners who visited our booth.
Congratulations to all the winners who won in our Lucky Draw. We are also glad to have made such impacting connections while enjoying the beautiful City of Sun City #CiscoConnectSSA #wearecomputech</description></item><item><title>Dell Tech Forum</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-tech-forum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-tech-forum/</guid><description>Computech was a Gold Sponsor during the Dell Tech Forum 9th April at Kempinski Hotel. We focused on show casing security analysis solutions by capturing great intel during the forum changing the way security surveillance is currently captured. There were great sessions from Key note speakers including a ‘Women in Tech session as well. Exciting Virtual Reality Gaming experience with Pro Series Gaming during the forum and so much more. Computech are officially Platinum Partners of Dell EMC #wearecomputech</description></item><item><title>Huawei Awards</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/huawei-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/huawei-awards/</guid><description>Computech was awarded 4 awards during the Huawei Technologies and Redington Africa Partner Summit on 27th March 2019: Gold Partner Award, Enterprise Partner of the year, Best Performing Sales Partner and Best Performing Pre-Sales Partner.
Computech CEO Hassan Popat spoke during the Summit saying, &amp;quot; We are excited to have worked on many projects jointly with Huawei especially with KCB Group. At Computech, we look forward to growing our relationship with Huawei across multiple sectors and industries all across East Africa.</description></item><item><title>Stanford Business School: Discovering Your Inner Strategic Leader</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/stanford-event/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/stanford-event/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Too many managers and executives view strategy as someone else&amp;rsquo;s job - perhaps the CEO and other members of the C-Suite, or perhaps a consulting firm. But any executive who makes resource allocation decisions is doing strategy, and any manager who wants to succeed in her career needs to master strategic thinking and decision making.&amp;rdquo;
Stanford Graduate School of Business in association with us, Computech Limited, were able to invite CEOs in Kenya for a Leadership Session on Discovering Your Inner Strategic Leader with speaker Professor Jesper Sørensen on January 29th, at the Capital Club Nairobi.</description></item></channel></rss>