<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>news on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/news/</link><description>Recent content in news on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 13:53:36 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Safeguard your Endpoint Devices with An Authorized Service Center you can Trust.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/safeguard-endpoint-devices-with-authorized-service-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 13:53:36 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/safeguard-endpoint-devices-with-authorized-service-center/</guid><description>Device wear and tear is inevitable. What happens when your servers are down and repair is half the cost of the initial server price? Your warranty is here to protect you, reduce repair time and eventually enhance organization productivity by reducing costs and enabling the staff to get back to working on what is important.
Cheap is expensive in the Long Run. Invest in quality services and a support partner who assures timely maintenance.</description></item><item><title>What is SASE?</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/what-is-sase/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 22:36:20 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/what-is-sase/</guid><description>Well, what is SASE? Secure access service edge combines networking and security functions in the cloud to deliver seamless, secure access to applications, anywhere users work. Core functions include software-defined wide area network, secure web gateway, firewall as a service, cloud access security broker, and zero-trust network access. The SASE model aims to consolidate these functions in a single, integrated cloud service.
Cisco is driving the revolution of secure access everywhere.</description></item><item><title>Red Hat Ansible</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/red-hat-ansible-content-creation-hub/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 21:02:41 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/red-hat-ansible-content-creation-hub/</guid><description>Smart Scalable &amp;amp; Sharable Automation The world as we know it has changed, and therefore so has the way in which we need to operate within it. Enterprises not only need the ability to easily create automation, but they also need to be able to share and reuse automation across projects and teams with the right level of governance and control.
Welcome to seamless automation with Red Hat Ansible Ansible Automation Platform provides an enterprise framework for building and operating IT automation at scale, from hybrid cloud to the edge.</description></item><item><title>Happy Easter!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-easter-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 17:14:39 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-easter-2022/</guid><description>On the pious occasion of Easter, we are more than happy to extend our warmest and positive easter greetings to our invaluable customers who have been loyal to us for decades.
Happy Easter and may you spend the day with all your loved ones.</description></item><item><title>Looking to Upgrade Your PC ? Look no Further, we’ve got you covered.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/upgrade-pc-with-hp-240-g8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 18:16:33 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/upgrade-pc-with-hp-240-g8/</guid><description>Looking to upgrade your PC this year without denting your wallet? We’ve got you covered with the HP 240 G8 for all your business tasks with a 10th Gen Intel® Core™ processor and essential collaboration tools. Get connected with the HP 240 Laptop PC with powerful technology and a streamlined chassis that’s easy to take everywhere you go.
Nice &amp;amp; Light The HP 240 Laptop keeps up with mobile workstyles with a thin and light design.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of doing a Preventive Maintenance Every Quarter.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/preventative-maintenance-every-quarter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 02:19:48 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/preventative-maintenance-every-quarter/</guid><description>Why should you schedule a PM each quarter? Personal Health and Hygiene Benefits. The first advantage is a bit obvious, but it’s worth mentioning. Bacteria, mold, and dust cause everything from allergies to asthma. Regular cleaning of computer will significantly lower the potential for sickness, and create a healthier environment overall.
Reduces overall PC Overheating. Cooling fans play a primary role in reducing heat in your PC. If dust and debris block the fan from rotating internal hardware won’t get cool air and the hot air can’t escape.</description></item><item><title>Symantec Security Solutions – More than just endpoint protection</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/symantec-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 11:23:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/symantec-security-solutions/</guid><description>Now more than ever Cyber security has become very important with more pervasive cyber-attacks occurring globally.
According to the IBM Report, the top 3 most common attacks were stolen credentials (20% of breaches), phishing (17%), and misconfigurations (15%). ~ The security intelligence.
There are now nearly 75x more phishing sites as there are malware sites.
Start this new year with Formidable security solutions. Book your Free Seat now to learn how you can start this new year with New Security goals that will comprehensively protect your Organization.</description></item><item><title>Happy Work Anniversary Dipak</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-30th-anniversary-dipak/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 20:21:05 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-30th-anniversary-dipak/</guid><description>We would like to celebrate Dipak Galaiya’s 30th work anniversary at Computech Limited. Dipak joined Computech in 1992 as a Chief accountant and within the 30 years of his industrious service, he has played an immense role in the integral success of Computech as a leading System Integrator in East &amp;amp; Southern Africa.
He has proudly mentored and continues to mentor numerous staff members from all walks of life who have gone on to achieve great strides in their professional careers.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Stability In Future- Ready Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/stability-future-read-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 01:24:41 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/stability-future-read-infrastructure/</guid><description>Red Hat Enterprise Linux is the world’s leading enterprise Linux platform. It’s an open-source operating system (OS). It’s the foundation from which you can scale existing apps and roll out emerging technologies across bare-metal, virtual, container and all types of cloud environments.
Red Hat Enterprise Linux reduces deployment friction and costs while speeding time to value for critical workloads, enabling development and operations teams to innovate together in any environment.</description></item><item><title>Embrace Your 2022 Security Goals.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/embrace-your-2022-security-goals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 23:07:14 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/embrace-your-2022-security-goals/</guid><description>A rise in remote employees and an increased reliance on SaaS applications create new, wider gaps in security. To put it simply, it’s more challenging to protect users at the edge — ensuring seamless connections that optimize productivity without creating performance issues that drag down user satisfaction. Enter the secure access service edge (SASE), an architectural approach that offers an alternative to traditional data center-oriented security.
SASE converges networking capabilities with cloud-native security functions to simplify deployment and streamline management in the cloud.</description></item><item><title>New Year, New IT Goals</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/new-year-new-it-goals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:14:46 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/new-year-new-it-goals/</guid><description>Nothing in tech is sure in the soonest long periods of 2020, hardly any industry specialists would have anticipated that the concentration for tech experts before very long would be on the quick arrangement of instruments to help boundless remote work.
In any case, notwithstanding unanticipated turns of events, pioneers in the tech business can generally detect forthcoming patterns.
From the continued technical support needed for remote and hybrid work, below are the 10 tech trends believed to dominate the commercial and consumer market in the year 2022.</description></item><item><title>Happy International Computer Security Day</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-international-computer-security-day-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 13:42:10 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-international-computer-security-day-2021/</guid><description>History of International Computer Security Day This important day in computer history was first celebrated in 1988 to make awareness of computer security. It was the time when computers became common worldwide, especially with the increased use of computers in business industries and government operations which hosted a large amount of sensitive user data &amp;amp; information.
At that point, the internet was in its genesis stage. During the early days of modern computers; hacking was not a common trend and most computer viruses were engineered as a prank.</description></item><item><title>We are here for you, every step of the way.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/we-are-here-for-you-every-step-of-the-way/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:02:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/we-are-here-for-you-every-step-of-the-way/</guid><description>We are delighted to announce that we are now officially a Huawei Gold Enterprise Partner across all our regions of operation. We are committed to delivering the utmost form of quality during our service delivery by fostering good relationships with technology partners by completing all quality checks, enablement activities, and engineer certifications.
We are here for you, every step of the way. Feel free to reach out on any Huawei Enterprise Solutions, we will be pleased to serve you.</description></item><item><title>Embrace the New Normal With Cisco Webex</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/embrace-the-new-normal-with-cisco-webex/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 21:16:55 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/embrace-the-new-normal-with-cisco-webex/</guid><description>Remember how we used to work Last Year? Work is much better now with the whole new Hybrid Model. Today&amp;rsquo;s good enough isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. Hybrid work is about adapting to how teams work best and creating experiences that reach everyone. Webex powers a new way of collaborating that’s centered around the work you do, not where you do it—whether it’s in the office, at home, or anywhere in between.
Call from any device.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for whatever comes next! Join the Dell Technologies Forum Emerging Africa.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-technologies-forum-emerging-africa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 17:30:58 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-technologies-forum-emerging-africa/</guid><description>Your digital future awaits at the Dell Technologies Forum Emerging Africa. Join us at Dell Technologies Forum Emerging Africa on 6/10/2021 to explore how data is driving new ways of living, learning and working from anywhere! Discover how Dell Technologies is transforming the IT experience to help you unleash the potential of a data centric tomorrow.
LEARN about the innovations that matter to you through visionary keynotes and interactive breakout sessions ENGAGE with the experts behind your favorite solutions and share your experiences with industry peers.</description></item><item><title>Combine a Dynamic Design With Reliable Performance Hp</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/combine-a-dynamic-design-with-reliable-performance-hp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:51:44 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/combine-a-dynamic-design-with-reliable-performance-hp/</guid><description>What Do you Get when you combine a dynamic Design &amp;amp; Reliable Performance?
Figure 1: HP Authorized Dealer, Reseller, Partner and Seller in Nairobi, Kenya , Kampala, Uganda , Tanzania &amp;amp; Zambia.
What do you get when you combine a dynamic design, reliable performance &amp;amp; multi-layered security? The HP ProBook 450 G8! The go-to PC for the fast-paced remote worker. Apart from its lightweight chassis and remarkable processing power, this PC is packed with commercial-grade security features that protect your data on the go, embracing the WFH culture.</description></item><item><title>Thank You for using the new secure Cisco Webex</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/thank-you-cisco-webex-partner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 16:28:41 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/thank-you-cisco-webex-partner/</guid><description>All We Can Say Is Thank you. We’d Like to take this opportunity to thank everyone who attended this interactive webinar.
Missed it? Don’t Worry, we’ve got you covered In case you missed it, you don’t have to worry. As a Cisco Premier Partner, we are here to ensure that you have the best experience while using our Cisco Solutions.
New Cisco Webex for Remote Collaboration/Communication Cisco Any Connect VPN Cisco Umbrella Cisco DUO Multifactor Authenticator Get Started COVID-19 isn’t going anywhere anytime soon.</description></item><item><title>Congratulations to the Kenyan Olympic Team</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/congratulations-to-the-kenyan-olympics-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 17:32:04 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/congratulations-to-the-kenyan-olympics-team/</guid><description>“To win is not important. To be successful is not even important. How to plan and prepare is crucial. When you plan very well and prepare very well, then success can come on the way. Then winning can come on your way.” - Eliud Kipchoge
We’d like to take this opportunity to appreciate all the efforts of our Kenyan athletes who are carrying our flag high at the Kenya Olympics.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Hybrid Work is Here!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/the-future-of-hybrid-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 12:59:29 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/the-future-of-hybrid-work/</guid><description>The COVID 19 pandemic has forced many businesses to transition to remote work. We all have to accept the fact that COVID 19 isn’t going away anytime soon, we have to adapt, be positive and thrive. Is your organization really prepared for this dynamic shift in the New Work Culture? Join us in this Interactive Webinar Hosted by CIO Africa where we will walk you through why Cisco Webex is trusted by 85% of the Fortune 500 companies (Ranging from formula one to CNN), enabling teams to work better, together in an affordable and secure manner.</description></item><item><title>Want to Learn How Robotic Process Automation can Transform your Industry? We've Got You Covered!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/robotic-processing-automation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:19:29 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/robotic-processing-automation/</guid><description>Gartner predicts that 90% of organizations globally will have adopted RPA in some form by 2022 as they look to digitally empower critical business processes through resilience and scalability, while recalibrating human labor and manual effort. “Gartner anticipates RPA demand to grow and service providers to more consistently push RPA solutions to their clients because of the impact of COVID-19,” said Cathy Tornbohm, distinguished research vice president at Gartner. “The decreased dependency on a human workforce for routine, digital processes will be more attractive to end users not only for cost reduction benefits, but also for insuring their business against future impacts like this pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Reimagine your workforce and the future of IT with Cisco Secure Remote Workforce Solutions.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/reimagine-your-workforce-with-cisco/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 15:16:41 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/reimagine-your-workforce-with-cisco/</guid><description>Today’s workforce is no longer bound to a primary workplace. Where people work, or their workspace, has shifted from desks in office buildings to make-shift offices at home.
Welcome to the Future of Hybrid Work with Cisco WebEx. WebEx powers a new way of collaborating that’s centered around the work you do, not where you do it—whether it’s in the office, at home, or anywhere in between.
Why Choose Cisco Webex over other Collaboration Solutions?</description></item><item><title>Learning Never Stops at Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/learning-never-stops-at-computech/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 13:23:10 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/learning-never-stops-at-computech/</guid><description>Learning never stops at Computech Limited. Especially, if you have committed team members who are always striving to educate themselves on new and emerging trends. The world of information security is always changing, you need to stay on top of your game to learn about new threats and technologies in the Cyber Security Space.
We took time to appreciate all the team members who successfully completed &amp;amp; passed the Symantec Data Loss Prevention &amp;amp; End Point Security Enablement - training sessions.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the Future of Network With Juniper Networks</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/welcome-to-the-future-of-network-with-juniper-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:18:27 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/welcome-to-the-future-of-network-with-juniper-networks/</guid><description>Stand a Chance to Win Amazon Vouchers worth 525$ in Our Interactive Juniper Webinar. Join Our Interactive Webinar where we will walk you through the following immersive topics:
Agenda Introduction to the Experience First Networking The AI-Driven Enterprise Mist Assurance and Marvis Virtual Network Assistant The AI-Driven WAN with 128T by Mist AI The Cloud Ready Data Center Power of Intent Based Networking and Analytics 5 Lucky Participants will stand a chance of winning Amazon Shopping Vouchers worth 525 $ .</description></item><item><title>Empower Your Remote Workforce with Cisco Secure Remote Workforce Solutions.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/empower-your-workforce-with-cisco-secure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 17:15:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/empower-your-workforce-with-cisco-secure/</guid><description>These uncertain times have caused a fundamental shift in the way we work. Offices are slowly opening back up. Some employees can&amp;rsquo;t wait to return, while others want to continue to work from home.
This remote work culture isn’t going away any time soon. We have given birth to the Hybrid Work culture that has been adopted and widely accepted to be much more productive than the in-office work culture. Despite a tumultuous year in 2020, remote workers report a Workforce Happiness Index of 75 out of 100, compared to 71 for in-office employees.</description></item><item><title>We are proud to Announce our Strategic Partnership with Servicetrace as an RPA Solution Provider.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-patners-with-servicetrace-rpa-solution-provider/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 09:58:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-patners-with-servicetrace-rpa-solution-provider/</guid><description>At Computech, we have been at the forefront of automation as an IT Service Provider for over 33 years in East Africa. With this in mind, we can assist you to be a pioneer and gain a competitive edge in your particular industry with Robotic Process Automation. Begin your fulfilling journey of deploying intelligent software robots with us.
Intelligent Software Robotics Start your Journey Here!
Robotic Process Automation Around 30% of all tasks can be automated.</description></item><item><title>Ongoing attacks are targeting unsecured mission-critical SAP apps. Is Your Organization Protected?</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/protect-sap-apps-vulnerabilities-mission-control/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 13:53:04 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/protect-sap-apps-vulnerabilities-mission-control/</guid><description>Threat actors are targeting mission-critical SAP applications unsecured against already patched vulnerabilities, exposing the networks of commercial and government organizations to attacks.
Over 400,000 orgs worldwide and 92% of Forbes Global 2000 use SAP&amp;rsquo;s enterprise apps for supply chain management (SCM), enterprise resource planning (ERP), product lifecycle management (PLM), and customer relationship management (CRM).
SAP and cloud security firm Onapsis warned of these ongoing attacks today, and have worked in partnership with the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and Germany&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity agency BSI to warn SAP customers to deploy patches and survey their environments for unsecured apps.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Fast Internet Connectivity is Here!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/huawei-air-engine-wifi-6-webinar-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 14:31:17 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/huawei-air-engine-wifi-6-webinar-2021/</guid><description>Do You Need Wi-Fi 6? You may sit down and wonder why you should get Huawei Wifi 6 yet you have an existing system in place. Well Air Engine Wifi 6 packs a lot of power in its functionality; an attribute on how it got its name.
Wi-Fi 6 (802.11ax) supports four times higher network bandwidth and user concurrency compared to Wi-Fi 5. And only Huawei Air Engine Wi-Fi 6 incorporates 5G-powered antenna and algorithm technologies to slash network latency — down from 30 ms to just 10 ms — eliminating any dizziness from the VR/AR experience, enabling wireless 4K HD conferences, and resulting in zero packet loss during AGV roaming.</description></item><item><title>Digital Assaults in Kenya up by 50% considerably to hit 56m in a quarter of a year. Are You Protected?</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/digital-assaults-in-kenya-up-by-50-percent/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 02:30:19 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/digital-assaults-in-kenya-up-by-50-percent/</guid><description>Digital assaults on Kenyan associations rose by almost 50% over the most recent three months of 2020, contrasted with a comparable period the earlier year, another information shows.
This came when associations embraced far-off working frameworks just as online business instruments in the midst of Covid-19 lockdown measures. The Communications Authority of Kenya (CA) information shows that in excess of 56 million digital dangers were distinguished cross country in contrast with 37.</description></item><item><title>We’re Happy to Announce our Strategic Partnership with Savic Technologies.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/partnering-with-savic-technologies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 21:48:37 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/partnering-with-savic-technologies/</guid><description>Computech and SAVIC Technologies are two organizations that share the same Business Values and saw this as a bridge that would foster a great Partnership. With over 33 Years in the market and a deep expertise on how to cater to client needs, we are proud to announce a new partnership designed to grow and enhance the ability to deliver world-class services to the Africa Market.
Who We Are ? (Savic Technologies) SAVIC Technologies is a global IT &amp;amp; SAP Consulting Company Providing complete end to end Implementation, Upgrade, Migration, Support and Custom Development on Various SAP technologies.</description></item><item><title>To New Cyber Security Beginnings.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/spire-solutions-partnership-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 16:54:24 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/spire-solutions-partnership-announcement/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce our Partnership with Spire Solutions as a Strategic Partner in East and Central Africa. A new addition to our Cyber Security Arsenal.
Spire Solutions: The Preferred Cyber Security Distributor in the Region. Spire Solutions is Middle East &amp;amp; Africa’s leading value-added distributor (VAD), with exclusive distribution rights for some of the world’s best-known vendors (OEMs) that offer niche cyber security solutions and services. We engage, empower and enable channel partners across Middle East &amp;amp; Africa via various partnership models and partner success programs.</description></item><item><title>It’s a New Year ! This means we have to adapt and implement the 2021 Security Goals. Don’t be left out.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/adapt-and-implement-2021-security-goals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 16:10:14 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/adapt-and-implement-2021-security-goals/</guid><description>Don’t miss the 2021 Cyber Security Bus. Let’s face it, the rate of Cyber Security threats isn’t plummeting. In fact, while 31% of companies worldwide reported being attacked daily during 2020, the rate of attacks targeting employees working remotely will only increase in 2021 as cybercriminals target less secure systems outside the corporate network to access an organization’s data.
A 2019 report from Microsoft concluded that 2FA works, blocking 99.9% of automated attacks.</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays From the Computech Family 2020</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-holidays-from-the-computech-family-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 17:47:25 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-holidays-from-the-computech-family-2020/</guid><description>Happy Holidays from The Computech Family! Looking back on this past year, we see just how lucky we are to have people like you supporting us. You are the backbone of our success.
Thank you so much for helping to shape our business. Computech would like to extend its warmest Christmas wishes to you and your family.
Please unplug, relax, and settle into an enjoyable holiday season.
Happy Holidays and Stay Safe.</description></item><item><title>Cisco Web Security Update</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/cisco-web-security-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 05:03:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/cisco-web-security-update/</guid><description>Proactively Protect your Company Data from Phishing attacks using Cisco Secure Email: Comprehensive Defense in this era of Sophisticated Cyber Attacks. As our screen time increases and constant communication over email platforms during this WFH period; hackers have taken their efforts a notch higher to target workers who do not have off premise security protection.
We’ve reported a whopping 73% growth in Email Phishing Attacks during the #COVID19 pandemic. This raises the sincere question: “Is your company and personal data comprehensively protected against email attacks?</description></item><item><title>A Class Apart: Stories that Made a difference.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/a-class-apart/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 08:45:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/a-class-apart/</guid><description>Dipak Galaiya, group chief commercial officer, computech limited, gives an overview of how the leading systems integrator supported university of nairobi in creating a comprehensive customer experience center.
The University of Nairobi (UON), one of the largest educational institutions based in Nairobi, Kenya, was seeking to centralize disjointed operations of its numerous departments. The students were following up with each department independently for different services, resulting in inefficiencies and delays. The collegiate research university needed to have a single point of contact for all the processes for students.</description></item><item><title>Accelerating Growth &amp; Building Resilience in Corporate Banking with Oracle Solutions.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/oracle-webinar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 02:10:21 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/oracle-webinar/</guid><description>Times are changing and as technology evolves at this exponential rate, it is clearly evident that there&amp;rsquo;s no need for a whole range of databases to deal with different application and data types.
A converged database saves you time and money while boosting efficiency and that is where we come to the rescue as an Oracle Partner, reseller and Distributor in Kenya, Tanzania and Uganda.
Optimize your Business performance outcomes with oracle solutions.</description></item><item><title>Don't be left out ! Work in style with the new HP Elite book 840 G6.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-elitebook-846-g6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:33:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-elitebook-846-g6/</guid><description>Looking to buy a laptop that not only offers style and durability but also packs performance? You can’t go wrong with the HP EliteBook 840 G6; this is where style meets performance.
The Hp EliteBook 840 G6 is built for the modern professional who is conscious about: user-targeted security, seamless performance, a durable yet light form-factor and enhanced collaboration features for meetings on the go.
Remote work doesn’t have to be boring with this EliteBook.</description></item><item><title>Cisco Any Connect</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/secure-your-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:54:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/secure-your-remote/</guid><description>Secure your remote workforce, fast Let’s face it, remote working is not going anywhere anytime soon. In fact, it is much easier and convenient to work remote and embrace this new digital era where everything is on the go. A recent Global Workforce Survey done by Cisco showed that 58% of the workforce expects to be working from home at least 8 days a month.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to embrace our new normal, a blend of in-office and remote workers in every meeting.</description></item><item><title>We are Not Yet out of the Woods, stay safe &amp; Flatten the curve with Computech Limited.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/covid-19-awareness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 13:08:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/covid-19-awareness/</guid><description>We have been strong and stayed together through these unprecedented times and as more restrictions are being lifted by worldwide governments, we need to exercise utmost caution to completely #flattenthecurve and avoid a second wave. Only you can help beat Covid-19. Here are some tips on how to prevent further infection and reinfection.
Tips to avoid Covid-19 Transmission. Stay safe by taking some simple precautions, such as:
Maintain at least a 1-metre distance between yourself and others Wearing a mask when interacting with people Keeping rooms well ventilated for aeration Avoiding crowds and unnecessary gatherings Cleaning your hands with Alcohol based sanitizers and soap Coughing into a bent elbow or tissue.</description></item><item><title>Protect your workforce with simple, powerful access security.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/protect-your-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:37:33 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/protect-your-workplace/</guid><description>Security is becoming more and more complex. That is why we need to adapt to modern cyber security trends to keep our businesses up to date with upcoming security threats.
80% of security breaches involve compromised passwords. Make sure your users are who they say they are. Verify your users with multi-factor authentication from Cisco Duo.
Keeping your employees safe and your business protected, is at the heart of what we do.</description></item><item><title>All we can Say Is Thank You ! We appreciate you for always putting the Customer First.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/customer-service-breakfast-2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 07:12:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/customer-service-breakfast-2020/</guid><description>Always expect a surprise while working at Computech Limited. At least that is what our staff got during the Customer Service Week. An early morning full course and scrumptious breakfast to appreciate them for their industrious culture and putting their foot forward to always serve the customer in a timely, hospitable and effective manner. Kudos to the computech Family for always putting the Customer First!
Staff Message by our GCCO Computech Staff Appreciation Breakfast.</description></item><item><title>Customer Service Week Blog (Customers)</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/customer-service-week-customers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 07:38:49 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/customer-service-week-customers/</guid><description>To all our clients, we wish you a very Happy Customer Service Week…. We promise to deliver you the best of services each and every time.
Without you, we wouldn’t be here. Feel free to always reach out on any service that you may require.
All we can say is thank you!</description></item><item><title>Happy Birthday to Computech’s Founder and Group CEO.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-birthday-computech-founder-group-ceo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 03:16:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/happy-birthday-computech-founder-group-ceo/</guid><description>We take this moment to wish Computech&amp;rsquo;s Founder and Group CEO a Happy Birthday 🎉🎂. With a vision to be Africa&amp;rsquo;s most respected and trusted technology provider for businesses; Hassan has been a key contributor in the East African IT industry since the inception of Computech in 1987.
Enabling high-performance organizations and businesses to work and communicate better, faster and more profitably.
Being a mentor to major CEOs, MDs and CIOs in the East African Tech industry, he has inspired and overseen numerous and notable Projects that have propelled the IT industry in East and Central Africa to greater heights.</description></item><item><title>Staying Productive While Working Remotely With Microsoft Teams</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/staying-productive-while-working-remotely-with-microsoft-teams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 10:08:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/staying-productive-while-working-remotely-with-microsoft-teams/</guid><description>Remote work isn’t going anywhere anytime soon. Let’s face this is the new normal-our current workplace reality. However, working remote doesn’t mean you have to be isolated. Here are a few tips to make your remote working experience worthwhile.
Getting started As you move to remote work, a few key habits will set you up for success.
Introduction Microsoft Teams
Set up your workspace If you don’t have a home office, don’t worry.</description></item><item><title>Your Number One and Trusted HP Authorized Service Centre in Kenya</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/your-number-one-hp-authorized-service-center-in-kenya/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 03:22:44 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/your-number-one-hp-authorized-service-center-in-kenya/</guid><description>Being a HP platinum partner, HP Authorized Service Centre and the first service center in East Africa to partner with Hewlett-Packard (HP), we assure on quality and loyal service as we walk you through our Service Delivery Journey.
Enjoy exclusive, affordable and reliable Service Centre Solutions for your Business ranging from:
1. Workshop Services Break and Fix services , PC consumables &amp;amp; Accessories Genuine spare parts and accessory replacements.
2. Specialized Warranty Support Services Business continuity for the end points assuring spare replacements, vendor firmware patch management.</description></item><item><title>Your Trusted Outsource Provider</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/your-trusted-outsource-provider/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 06:07:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/your-trusted-outsource-provider/</guid><description>Your Trusted IT Outsource Provider Is your company looking for highly skilled IT Services but also trying to maintain a budget friendly cost while doing so? Maybe you want a quarterly IT Maintenance service or a Temporary IT staff to work on a dedicated project.
Computech Limited has got you covered. With notable clients in the:
BFSI Market IT Industry Hospitality Industry Manufacturing Industry Pharmaceutical Industry Sacco Industry We have experience in the IT Outsource sector, providing highly skilled IT Outsource Services to notable companies.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft 365: A subscription to make the most of your time</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-office-365-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:36:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-office-365-2020/</guid><description>You can’t make more time. But with Microsoft 365, you can make more of your time. Because planning a night with your friends shouldn’t take all day.
Organizing your day doesn’t have to take up most of it. And time spent worrying about the safety of your family, could be time spent with your family as you work from home.
How does Microsoft 365 Help you do this? Microsoft 365 helps you make more of your time by combining premium Office apps with innovations in Outlook, Microsoft Teams, OneDrive and Family Safety.</description></item><item><title>Dragonfly With Computech</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dragonfly-with-computech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 18:42:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dragonfly-with-computech/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Don’t Miss the IOT Bus- Transform before you have to.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dont-miss-the-iot-bus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 11:26:29 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dont-miss-the-iot-bus/</guid><description>We are proud to officially announce that Computech Limited has set foot into the Internet of Things Market.
The IoT managed services market was US$ 30.2Billion in 2018 and is anticipated to grow at a Compound Annual Growth Rate of 18.5% to account for US$ 135 Billion by 2025.
Don’t miss the IOT bus. Start your journey today with Computech and grow your future business with new-age technologies.
Book your free consultation session with our Internet of Things Consultant to shed more light into how your business can adapt to the rapidly changing market by leveraging the power of IOT.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Next-Gen Top Security Orchestration and Automation Response Platform for Client Value</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/d3-security-next-generation-soar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 19:34:31 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/d3-security-next-generation-soar/</guid><description>We are proud to announce our New business Partnership with D3 Security. Frost and Sullivan, a global research and consulting firm, recently named D3 Security’s Next-Generation SOAR Platform as the Top SOAR Solution for Client Value.
Read the Frost and Sullivan SOAR Report – and learn how the combination of security orchestration, automation and response with the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK framework maximized value for SOAR customers.
What makes it Different from the other SOAR Platforms?</description></item><item><title>Flatten the Curve With Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/flatten-the-curve-with-computech-ltd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:22:56 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/flatten-the-curve-with-computech-ltd/</guid><description>Flatten the Curve with Computech Limited As the cessation of movement in and out of Nairobi is lifted, we need to be cautious enough to flatten the curve effectively. Your safety is our priority.
Stay safe, stay home, sanitize and avoid unnecessary movement and together we will get through this.
Kindly follow the recommended WHO and Government safety measures and together we will flatten the Curve ⚕️
#wearecomputech #computechcares #staysafe #flattenthecurve #safetyfirst #covid19 #maskup #2020 #fbf #newnormal Contact Us Feel free to contact us on any:</description></item><item><title>Sabasaba Day</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/sabasaba-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 13:37:14 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/sabasaba-day/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We are not makers of history. We are made by history.” Martin Luther King, Jr.
History Teaches us Lessons. Positive ones that we can build on to become greater individuals &amp;amp; strive to build our nation. We take this opportunity to commemorate all those who put their lives on the frontline of the Multi-party struggle with a vision of a democratic republic and a country that embraces political freedom.
Where there is unity there is always victory.</description></item><item><title>Thank You for putting Your Trust in Us.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/thanks-for-trusting-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:25:04 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/thanks-for-trusting-us/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;If everyone is moving forward together, then success takes care of itself.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Henry Ford
Teamwork is the ability to work together towards a common vision. The ability to direct individual accomplishments toward organizational objectives. It is the fuel that allows common people to attain uncommon results.
That&amp;rsquo;s why here at Computech Limited we believe in One Team focused and tirelessly working together to achieve One Dream.
A dream to become Africa&amp;rsquo;s most respected and trusted provider of technology for businesses.</description></item><item><title>Safeguard Your Staff and Clients from Covid-19 Infection with our Non-Contact Infrared Thermometer.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computechs-non-contact-infrared-thermometer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 18:40:26 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computechs-non-contact-infrared-thermometer/</guid><description>Introducing the Non-Contact Infrared Thermometer for your Business Premises. Currently, there is an unprecedented increase in Temperature Scans happening around the world due to circumstances resulting from COVID-19 (Coronavirus disease).
Computech Limited is here to safeguard the lives of your clients and workers with our Non-contact Infrared Forehead thermometer solution.
Why this Infrared Thermometer Solution? Not only is it FDA (Food and Drug Administration) approved, it has the following unique features that make it stand out from any other Infrared Thermometers:</description></item><item><title>Your users have left the building. Are they protected?</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/security-should-limit-threats-not-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 13:57:50 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/security-should-limit-threats-not-your-business/</guid><description>The modern workplace is ever changing and evolving from the Traditional 9-5 desk job, to a remote working culture where one is always on the go.
The transition might be challenging at first, but inevitably this working culture is here to stay. Putting in mind that the Corona Virus Pandemic has been a fundamental catalyst in speeding up this workplace revolution. Permanent desk jobs are now phrases coined in the past.</description></item><item><title>Computech Limited Is here to Assist with Your Remote Working Needs.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/work-remotely-dell-technologies-computech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 16:28:02 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/work-remotely-dell-technologies-computech/</guid><description>Like you, we are following COVID-19 closely. Keeping our team members, communities and customers safe is our first priority.
One way we are addressing the uncertainty of COVID-19 is encouraging our employees who can, to work from home. Many of you are looking to do the same and are reaching out to us for advice on the right remote working solutions.
Remote Working Solutions that Actually Work for you. As you work to arm more of your teams with the ability to work remotely, Computech Limited would like to share some key elements of our work-from-home program, many of which organizations of all sizes have also adopted with Dell Technologies Remote Work Solutions.</description></item><item><title>Hp Elitebook 830 G6 Notebook Pc, the Standout Business Pc</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-elitebook-830-g6-notebook-pc-the-standout-business-pc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 14:27:54 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-elitebook-830-g6-notebook-pc-the-standout-business-pc/</guid><description>Work from Anywhere in Style. The HP EliteBook 830 is designed for the modern mobile professional, the HP EliteBook 830 is a highly secure and manageable PC offering powerful collaboration tools, enabling the enterprise workforce to be more productive and secure on the go or in the office.
This specific laptop is suited for your travel needs and enables you to work securely from home during this sensitive period of the Corona virus outbreak.</description></item><item><title>Gain a Competitive Edge Through I.T. Automation with Red Hat Ansible</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/red-hat-ansible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:59:38 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/red-hat-ansible/</guid><description>Red Hat Premium Business Partner. We are proud to announce that we are officially a Red Hat Premium Business Partner. Feel free to contact us on any of your Red Hat business needs. We will be happy to assist you.
Do More with Automation. Taking into consideration of the unprecedented COVID-19 Crisis, movement has been limited due the Work from Home Policy. The need for I.T. Automation has risen due to the evolving remote-work culture.</description></item><item><title>Safeguard the Lives of your Staff and Clients with the Automated, Non-Touch Fever Kit Solution</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/automated-non-touch-fever-kit-for-staff-clients/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 10:25:03 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/automated-non-touch-fever-kit-for-staff-clients/</guid><description>Currently, there is an unprecedented increase in Temperature Scans happening around the world due to circumstances resulting from COVID-19 (Coronavirus disease). The World Health Organization recommends a 1-meter social distancing measure to curb the spread of this deadly virus during the Temperature Scanning process.
Human beings are prone to error during the scanning process as it might be quite tiresome. Therefore, the social distancing rule might be broken due to fatigue arising from the tasking procedure, further endangering the lives of your staff and clients.</description></item><item><title>Eid Mubarak!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/eid-mubarak-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 16:11:22 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/eid-mubarak-2020/</guid><description>Computech Limited would like to take this moment to wish you a happy Eid ul Fitr. As you break your fast, remember to stay safe and stay home as you celebrate this Holy Day.
Sanitize, maintain social distancing measures and be cautious and eventually we will eventually flatten the curve.
This is the day when we should pay gratitude to the divine light for all the wonderful things around us. Let this day bring new hope and opportunities in your life.</description></item><item><title>Be Assured of Savings in 60 Days with Computech Cloud Solutions.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/save-with-computech-solutions-60-days/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:47:39 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/save-with-computech-solutions-60-days/</guid><description>Currently, there is an unprecedented increase in cloud solution utilization happening around the world due to circumstances resulting from COVID-19 (Coronavirus disease).
This sensitive situation will require numerous budget cuts in specific departments in your organization but this should not worry you, as we are here to assist in your business transformation and innovation with Computech Cloud Solutions.
With the current budget crunch, saving cash in your Company’s IT spending is of the greatest essence.</description></item><item><title>HP DRAGONFLY. LIGHTER THAN AIR.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-dragonfly-lighter-than-air/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-dragonfly-lighter-than-air/</guid><description>HP DRAGONFLY. LIGHTER THAN AIR. The HP Elite Dragonfly gives a new level of freedom to those on-the-go. This beautifully designed, ultralight business convertible laptop in a stunning dragonfly blue finish features an ultrabright display and advanced security to help keep you safe and productive wherever the day takes you.
Ultralight and ready to impress The HP Elite Dragonfly provides mobility beyond expectation in an ultralight x360 touch laptop.</description></item><item><title>Committed to Service as Your number one Service Centre Since 1987</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-limited-celebrating-33-years-of-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-limited-celebrating-33-years-of-service/</guid><description>As we celebrate our 33rd Year as the Leading East African Systems Integrator, we are truly honoured to be at your service as the First Authorized Warranty Centre in Kenya.
Being a HP platinum partner and the first service centre in East Africa to partner with Hewlett-Packard (HP), we assure on quality and loyal service as we walk you through our Service Delivery Journey.
The Services that We Offer We are committed to round the clock service delivery (24hours), offering the following wide variety of Services:</description></item><item><title>Learning Never Stops with HP Be Online</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/learning-never-stops-with-hp-be-online/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/learning-never-stops-with-hp-be-online/</guid><description>Currently, there is an unprecedented increase in Remote Learning happening around the world due to circumstances resulting from COVID-19 (Coronavirus disease). If you&amp;rsquo;re carrying out your institutional Classes &amp;amp; Lectures remotely - we’re here to keep you, your students and your tutors connected to ensure that they don’t miss out on any crucial lessons with HP Be Online, the Best innovative E-Learning Software.
Our students need to prepare for the future and we must provide smarter educational solutions to support them.</description></item><item><title>Flatten the Curve with Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/committed-to-service-during-the-corona-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/committed-to-service-during-the-corona-outbreak/</guid><description>Computech Limited stands in solidarity with all the victims and individuals affected by the COVID-19 Pandemic. We understand the importance of staying at home to protect your life and that of others.
That is why we are committed to provide IT service Delivery and Support with the utmost safety and care while maintaining the recommended WHO safety measures during this sensitive period. Our staff are equipped with the state-of-the-art corona virus safety gear to safeguard the health of you and your employees during any IT site support.</description></item><item><title>May the spirit of Ramadan light up your soul. Happy Ramadan!</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-limited-wishes-you-ramadan-kareem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-limited-wishes-you-ramadan-kareem/</guid><description>Computech Limited wants to wish you a Happy Ramadan. Wishing a blessed Ramadan that will inspire you with courage and strength that will help you to win every challenge of life!
As you pray and fast at home with your family and friends, may Allah ease your hardships and shower you with loads of peace and prosperity during this Holy month of Ramadan.
Stay Safe, Sanitize and Maintain the recommended Social Distance during fellowship and gatherings in this Holy Month of Ramadan to protect yourself and your Muslim Brothers &amp;amp; Sisters from the Covid-19 Virus.</description></item><item><title>Dell Technologies Hyperconverged Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-technologies-hyperconverged-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/dell-technologies-hyperconverged-infrastructure/</guid><description>Make Innovation real and Modernize IT with Dell Technologies Hyperconverged Infrastructure. Modernize IT with proven Hyperconverged infrastructure solutions from Dell Technologies. New to a Hyper-converged Infrastructure? A Hyper-converged infrastructure also known as HCI is an infrastructure system with a software-centered architecture that integrates: computer, storage, networking, and virtualization into a single commodity hardware supported by a single vendor.
Why should you integrate a Hyper Converged Infrastructure into Your Business? As we approach this era of the remote working culture, we need virtualization in nearly everything.</description></item><item><title>This is why you should get your Business Connected to the New Cisco Webex</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/why-you-should-get-your-business-connected-to-the-new-cisco-webex/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/why-you-should-get-your-business-connected-to-the-new-cisco-webex/</guid><description>Introducing Cisco Webex, Hassle-free video conferencing that just works. Currently, there is an unprecedented increase in remote work happening around the world due to circumstances resulting from COVID-19 (Coronavirus disease). If you&amp;rsquo;re being asked to work remotely – Computech is here to keep your team connected on any device, enabling you to keep working from anywhere, at any time.
Welcome to Cisco Webex an application and communication tool that enables you to: Video-chat, meet, share files and work remotely, either on your phone or your PC.</description></item><item><title>Computech is HPE’s Overall Partner of the Year</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-hpe-s-overall-partner-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-hpe-s-overall-partner-of-the-year/</guid><description>The HPE Africa Tour is an annual roadshow during which HPE recognises outstanding partners and thanks customers for their support. This year, the awards for English speaking Africa (East &amp;amp; Southern Africa) was held in Nairobi.
It was attended by James Munene, HPE MD, and Jean Serbatian, HPE Africa Channel Manager. 10 awards were given to partners and Computech won 3 of those awards. Computech won the Storage Partner Award, the Server Partner Award, and the most prestigious award of the day – Overall Partner of the Year 2018.</description></item><item><title>Computech Profile on Africa Outlook</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-profile-on-africa-outlook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-profile-on-africa-outlook/</guid><description>Computech Limited is demonstrating ongoing entrepreneurial flair and an enthusiasm for technological innovation in order to combat a rapidly shifting IT landscape
Writer: Matthew Staff
Project Manager: Kane Weller
Computech Limited’s evolution over the past 30 years has been largely representative of the development of computing in general, the Company applying its wide range of technological expertise in an East African region progressing at a rapid pace.
The privately held Company, from its Kenyan, Zambian, Ugandan, Rwandan and Tanzanian hubs, has placed an equally prominent emphasis on wider skills development in the region over the years in order to ensure not just business growth, but overall infrastructural development.</description></item></channel></rss>