<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cyber security on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/cyber-security/</link><description>Recent content in cyber security on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/cyber-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4 Reasons to plan for a next-generation firewall with Computech</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/4-reasons-to-plan-for-a-next-generation-firewall-with-computech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/4-reasons-to-plan-for-a-next-generation-firewall-with-computech/</guid><description>Today’s cyber threat landscape of new threats and sophisticated attacks constantly being directed at your network renders traditional port-based firewalls ineffective.
Increasing sophistication of IT infrastructure and the rising concern of data security means that businesses now need solutions that can put them back in control by enabling full visibility over their networks and ones that reduce complexities and inefficiencies.
As one of the leading IT solution providers in the region, Computech has prioritized IT security and has been proactively engaging with customers to fully understand how we can solve their most pressing security needs while saving costs.</description></item><item><title>5 Reasons to Adopt a Cloud Backup Solution with Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/5-reasons-to-adopt-a-cloud-backup-solution-with-computech-limited/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/5-reasons-to-adopt-a-cloud-backup-solution-with-computech-limited/</guid><description>Protecting enterprise data is essential for survival of any business. With the ever-increasing threats of cyberattacks, businesses without a sound data backup and disaster recovery plan are continuing to lose critical assets and their competitive edge. However, traditional methods of data protection have been proven to be difficult, unreliable, and expensive, especially with the large volume of data that modern businesses now store and process.
There is a solution though! Thanks to cloud technologies, businesses can now benefit from fast, secure, and reliable disaster recovery plans while reducing costs and downtime.</description></item><item><title>Petya Ransomware: Another Reason to Protect your Technology</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/petya-ransomware-another-reason-to-protect-your-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/petya-ransomware-another-reason-to-protect-your-technology/</guid><description>As the world is coming to terms with the damage caused by WannaCry, the ransomware that crippled many businesses across the globe, another major cyber security attack has hit the headlines, with over 64 countries affected so far!
Petya, as the new ransomware has been nicknamed, has continued to disrupt businesses and bring organisations to a standstill. The malware is reported to exploit the same vulnerability in computers running on the unpatched version of the Windows Operating System just like its predecessor WannaCry.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Security: 6 Tactics to keep your technology safe</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/cyber-security-6-tactics-to-keep-your-technology-safe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/cyber-security-6-tactics-to-keep-your-technology-safe/</guid><description>The recent WannaCry ransomware attack that affected over 100, 000 computers across the world has shown just how vital an effective cyber security strategy is for any forward thinking organization. It has brought into focus key elements of cyber defense such as Patch Management, Network Filtering, Antivirus Protection, Backups, Staff Security Awareness Training and a comprehensive Incident Response Plan.
Becoming the target of a cyber attack is not a question of if, but when, an organization will be attacked.</description></item></channel></rss>