<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Us on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/</link><description>Recent content in About Us on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awards</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/awards/</guid><description>HP Top Revenue 2008
HP Special Award Enterprises Servers &amp;amp; Storage 2008 - 2009
Top 100 Mid-Sized Companies (KE) 2009
HP Top Revenue 2009
HP Top Revenue 2010
Microsoft Mid-Market Partner of the Year 2012
HP Platinum Partner 2014
Superbrands of Kenya 2015
HP Platinum Partner 2015
Microsoft EDA Enterprise Direct Advisor 2016
HP Computing Hardware Winner 2016
Microsoft Partner of the Year – Cloud Productivity in WECA 2017</description></item><item><title>Careers</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/careers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/careers/</guid><description>Please Note No fee is required when applying for a position Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Incomplete applications will not be considered The closing date for all applications is 3rd June 2022 Business Development Manager (Uganda) Looking to Join the Computech Family? Join us as a Business Development Manager in Uganda, where you will have the opportunity to formulate Sales strategies and manage a dynamic sales team to help them achieve their targets, goals, and quarterly revenues while also interacting with notable IT brands such as HP, Dell, Cisco, Huawei and many more.</description></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/downloads/</guid><description>ABOUT COMPUTECH CUSTOM SOFTWARE CYBER SECURITY MICROSOFT PORTFOLIO Computech Company Profile 2022 More info about Computech Company Profile 2022
DOWNLOAD iLoyalty More info about iLoyalty
DOWNLOAD iPricing More info about iPricing
DOWNLOAD proof of delivery More info about proof of delivery
DOWNLOAD Cyber Security More info about Cyber Security
DOWNLOAD Cyber Security Flyer More info about Cyber Security Flyer</description></item><item><title>Profile</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/profile/</guid><description>About Us Founded in 1987, Computech Limited is a leading East African systems integrator, providing technology solutions to solve businesses’ most important problems.
Celebrating 30 years since inception, Computech Limited has now expanded to have offices in 5 countries and a significant regional footprint.
Computech has significant experience across industry sectors, products and services, with substantial work done in providing professional services, infrastructure solutions, technical support, and technology outsourcing to all sectors.</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/about-us/team/</guid><description>One Team, One Dream Hassan Popat GROUP CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER (GCEO) The founder of Computech Limited, Hassan has led the Group to 7 offices and 250 staff, while continuing to grow the business from strength to strength. Hassan is well conversant with the global and local East African IT market and has extensive experience in handling large corporate clients. Hassan holds a BSc from Imperial College London and an MBA from Carnegie Mellon.</description></item></channel></rss>