<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>news on Computech Limited</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/news/</link><description>Recent content in news on Computech Limited</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.computechlimited.com/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP DRAGONFLY. LIGHTER THAN AIR.</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-dragonfly-lighter-than-air/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/hp-dragonfly-lighter-than-air/</guid><description>HP DRAGONFLY. LIGHTER THAN AIR. The HP Elite Dragonfly gives a new level of freedom to those on-the-go. This beautifully designed, ultralight business convertible laptop in a stunning dragonfly blue finish features an ultrabright display and advanced security to help keep you safe and productive wherever the day takes you.
Ultralight and ready to impress The HP Elite Dragonfly provides mobility beyond expectation in an ultralight x360 touch laptop.</description></item><item><title>Computech awarded with the oracle Field Delivery Partner Status (FDP)</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-awarded-with-the-oracle-field-delivery-partner-status/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-awarded-with-the-oracle-field-delivery-partner-status/</guid><description>Computech Limited, leading IT integrator in East Africa and a Gold member of Oracle Partner Network (OPN) for Oracle products and technology in Kenya, with a presence Tanzania Uganda and Zambia is now officially an authorized Field Delivery Partner (FDP) for Oracle as of July 2019. This partnership is a mark of excellence signifying the company’s in-depth experience working with Oracle’s technology. This partnership serves as an exceptional achievement and signals continuous growth for a company that has established its presence in the tech industry for over 30 years.</description></item><item><title>Join Computech Limited during 2019's Cisco Connect in South Africa</title><link>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-cisco-connect-south-africa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.computechlimited.com/computech-cisco-connect-south-africa/</guid><description>Cisco Connect is a global Cisco initiative that delivers inspiration, technical contents and industry insights to technology visionaries. Cisco Connect conference, will explore the opportunities and challenges presented by this dynamic region’s aspirations and how adopting the right technologies can help local businesses succeed regionally and globally.
The conference will feature a diverse range of activities, including keynotes from prominent speakers, technical breakout sessions, showcases of exciting new products, and off-site visits.</description></item></channel></rss>